I don't know, Nick.
You're the accountant.
- These books...
- Yeah, I know.
- Hello?
- I'm not sure.
Hello, there! Excuse me!
I just wonder if... Hel...
It'll be different this time.
Honestly.
The accounts are in order.
OK. I'll see you in an hour. OK. Bye.
- Now...
- Those books, how much?
- Hm?
- The leather-bound books.
The Collected Works
of Charles Dickens.
- They're real leather?
- They're real Dickens.
I have to know because
they have to go with a sofa.
Everything else in my house is real.
I'll give you 200.
- 200 what?
- £200.
Are they leather-bound pounds?
- No.
- They won't go with my wallet.
Next!
- Hello!
- Hello.
I need The Little Book of Calm,
do you have it?
I'm late for work. Uh, Calm...
Er, is this it?
No, no, it's just...
Too big, too big.
Little... just little...
- This one, this?
- No! No, calm.
- The Little Book of Calm.
- Er, this?
That's the one! Yes!
- Two-fifty.
- Two-fifty...
- Could...
- I'll just get you a bag.
No, no - no bag, just the book!
- I'll do you a receipt.
- No, that's fine!
It's broken. I'll write one.
Little...
I'll do it!
Calm, two-fifty. Thank you.
(Muttering frantically)
"Let-let-let go once in a while,
"you are a loose lily
floating down an amber river."
Sorry. I hate my job.